I spent the evening at groundswell a
social enterprise school of sorts that I
attended two years ago and listening to
the current six core part to speak about
their projects and businesses I wrote
down a few ideas one of which is now
sitting in spot 29 of my apples so now
I've got to talk about it and I have
there are two people there that were you
see so early childhood educators bad two
projects I'm thinking about it's having
an app of child child care cooperative
so being able to coordinate with other
people other parents to decide what we
need child care whether that's a
temporary babysitter or a nanny share or
anything else figuring out how to make
it work as a community child care
so child care cooperative app website is
Apple number 29